Okay, so hello everyone in the last video, but I've actually done is in the home page as you can see is chat container
component was ended twice because I've written it twice. That's why and
That's that is in and also our back in is actually failing because we haven't
Like the this a MongoDB network error, so I will fix it soon, but okay, so I will just fix it and I will come back
Okay, guys now the MongoDB is working and one thing is
Wait a second so here in the cluster. There's a setting called current IP address, okay
So whenever some MongoDB error network arises, so you need to whitelist the IP address
There would be some option that would be given. Okay. That's why I am trying to switch to you like sometimes the back end is running into an error because of these issues
so now
We have done with this. So let's just start with another component, so before that
Let's go to our web apps who it would be here in the front and side
So as we can see there's lots of errors that have been here on the right side
Let's go to and log in there as you can see the user face access fully and all the list users have been on the left side
So let's style this no chat selected component first because looking quite odd
so
Let's go let's close this back in folder. Let's go to the no chat selected and for this
That this thing would be in order to get things in center. You know the concept of Flexbox right
so you can apply flex flex
Yeah flex call and
Justify center in order to bring the
components to center and
What else we can do item center item center and then height should be full
Controllers, let's take a look at it
So we'll come to chat up this your homepage where you can start chatting with your friends. Okay, that one is fine and
What we can actually do in order to make it more look clear, so we can do
We can wrap everything around the dip so take this dip and
Wrap it around this h1 and p. So now let's make one another class name here
so this also flex flex call and
Justify center in order to bring the contents to center just t file
Center and text should be white
For these items and a padding while let's take it around
five and items should be center
So let's see this
It's good only and
For this day we have actually done for the h1 and p also have to do some styling. So let's increase the text
Length okay, so text side should be 3x cell
good now after this
Text should be white which is already white. We don't need to change it and
Then margin bottom. There's some margin. We should apply so it would be for
That's looking good and now
For this padding class. Let's also apply some styling. So class name and now
In this one text should be gray. I guess it should be good
400 and margin bottom would be four
Okay, let's look at this
Okay, this one is very good now after this
Since we have already styled this no chat selected component. There's one thing which we would like to do
in the sidebar you go first
Let's go to this sidebar and we are going to
Take the selected users and we are going to take the set set selected users as well. So for this one
Selected user selected
Use a from the chat store. Okay
So after this what we are actually going to do
One thing is here like for the users. We are actually mapping right
So we can see this for the users mapping. We don't have like for the button part
We need to actually do something so for that we are going to use a key value and
With this one user dot underscore ID
So
Actually, we are going to do for this like online and
For that one so if we click on that one it should display some results here. That's why we actually we are doing for that
You will understand that
Let me first do something for it. So
This one is actually never used and we need to make for it
So after this for the button part we are going to use some
Okay, so let's apply that on click method here as well. So on click
And with the on click
Set selected users
We are going to work on that also
selected user
And in this one you pass the user
Okay
So on selected user it should be a callback function. So call back function and now
Let's work on that. So
This is also going to get a input from there. Okay
So set
Selected user
Now let's work on this set selected user. Okay
So let's go here and this
Chat store. I think I've already worked on that. Okay. Nice set selected user user
And it's
Going to take one user and it is going to set using the use time methods. Okay, so that is one
Please type this one line of code
And
After this what we are going to actually we do is let's go to the sidebar again and
Okay, this selected user. I don't think we are going to use that. So we can actually remove
So this one should be fine and after this let's go here and on click
We have already done that for set selected user and for the user part
So now all the work that has been left is for that is chat header. Okay, so we are going to just import the chat store
From the chat store and let's take all the users from there. So const
Selected user whatever the selected user we have selected user
Equals to chat store. Okay, so in the chat store. Let's
We have taken the selected users and we are going to replace this user name and also for this online status
But first let's
Take this source
image so
selected
Selected user
dot profile pic
Selected user or profile pic. I could be fine and after this
For this user name also
Selected user dot user name
Okay, and
After this this online status. We can fix it later
And I think this should be good and for the messages part also we need to do the same thing for the go into this message. It is dot a GSX and
Import
Chat store okay chat store
From
dot dot slash store
Last chat store. Okay, this is good and
After this um
Since we are doing the same thing so
selected users
Selected user equal to
And chat store
From the chat store. We are getting the selected users and for the selected users
We are going to do the same thing like what this source here. Let's remove this one and
Let's apply some curly braces and inside of that selected users dot profile picture
Whatever they have currently it will be like blank because for all the users we haven't done anything
Okay
So
Wait a second and after this we are going to take one log user. Okay, so log user that would be also be present there from the chat store
So get the chat store and
This log user where it should be used in the outgoing right so go to their sample image remove this one and
Use the curly braces and after this
We can do that select not selected user logged user dot profile pic
Profile pic control safe
Let's go to our app
Log out. Let's take another
Okay, let's do one thing sign up
John Doe
at the rate. Okay, John Doe
Okay
John Doe at the rate of gmail.com
Set some password
Sign up
So as we can see here that in the
Online section. Let's present. I think we are running to some error
Let's debug this one. So inspect go to the console. I guess type or account read properties of a device profile pic
Act messages dot j632
Messages dot j6 let's go to this one
And we have done something wrong. I guess
logged user, right
Then why it's showing some
Issue okay, that's because it should be odds to actually
Right
That
Now as you can see that
Faggots IQ emulator at the right of so if you click this we can see that the state is showing online and that's
You can
Stive some messages, but it's not going to work now
Okay, now so this one is enough for the video. I guess you understood everything
We'll meet in the next video